Guide to the Collège de la Sainte Famille Collection AD.MC.028
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- The altar of the Cordi Jesu Catholic church. 32.2 x 23.3 cm, Undated; 11752; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1461)
  Photographic Prints; Churches; Religious Sites; Religious Crosses; Gelatin Silver Prints; Religious Imagery; Cairo, Egypt
- Students in a classroom., 1940; 11754; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1463)
  Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Teachers; Schools/Education; Students; Boys; Men; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Group portrait of clergymen., 1948; 11757; Collège de la Sainte Famille, Helwan, Cairo, Egypt (Object AD_MC_028_ref1466)
  Priests/Clergymen; Men; Italian Writing; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair